OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 20) 6178/020
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Public agreements: Code nos.820346-820794 (Box 40)
  - 820722, 2004-2006 (Box 40, Folder 43)
    County of Fresno
  - 820785, 2001-2004 (Box 40, Folder 44)
    Hamilton County Board of Education
  - 820793, 2000-2004 (Box 40, Folder 45)
    County of Alameda
  - 820794, 2002-2005 (Box 40, Folder 46)
    Miami Dade County
  - Folder List Index Box # 40 (Box 40, Folder 47)
- Private agreements: Code nos.8448-8648 (Box 41)
  - 8448, 2002-2006 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    July 1 2002 - June 30 2006
  - 8457, 2002-2006 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    April 1 2002 - March 31 2006
  - 8460, 2003-2006 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    6/1/2003 - 5/31/2006
  - 8467, 2002-2006 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    6/16/2002 - 6/15/2006
  - 8468, 2002-2006 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - 8480, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    June 2003
  - 8495, 2002-2006 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    4/1/2002 - 3/31/2006
  - 8496, 2002-2006 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - 8503, 1999-2006 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    7/1/1999 - 6/30/2006
  - 8507, 2001-2006 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    June 1 2001 - May 31 2006
  - 8509, 2002-2006 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    6/1/2002 - 5/31/2006
  - 8514, 2001-2006 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    September 1 2001 - July 31 2006
  - 8520, 2002-2006 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - 8521, 2001-2006 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - 8523, 2003-2006 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    October 1 2003 - September 30 2006
  - 8527, 2003-2006 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - 8529, 2003-2006 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    June 1 2003 - May 31 2006
  - 8542, 2002-2006 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    6/24/2002 - 6/30/2006
  - 8547, 2001-2006 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - 8548, 2002-2006 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - 8553, 2003-2006 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    9/1/2003 - 8/31/2006
  - 8558, 2000-2006 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    September 16 2000 - September 15 2006
  - 8583, 2003-2006 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - 8597, 2001-2006 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - 8598, 2001-2006 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    October 1 2001 - June 1 2006
  - 8599, 2004-2006 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    June 1 2004 - May 31 2006
  - 8600, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - 8603, 2001-2006 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - 8608, 2003-2006 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    May 5 2003 - April 30 2006
  - 8610, 2001-2006 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - 8617, 2001-2006 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - 8618, 2001-2006 (Box 41, Folder 32)
    May 1 2001 - April 30 2006
  - 8627 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - 8628 (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - 8630, 2003-2006 (Box 41, Folder 35)
    5/1/2003 - 4/30/2006
  - 8646, 2001-2006 (Box 41, Folder 36)
    5/1/2001 - 4/30/2006
  - 8648, 2001-2006 (Box 41, Folder 37)
- Public agreements: Code nos.820225-820322 (Box 42)
  - 820225, 2001-2004 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    Mendocino County Board of Supervision
  - 820227, 2000-2003 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    City of Santa Cruz
  - 820236, 2002-2005 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    City of San Diego
  - 820237, 2002-2005 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - 820238, 2003-2005 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - 820239, 2002-2005 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - 820240, 2000-2004 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    Trenton Board of Education
  - 820241, 2002-2004 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    City of Miami
  - 820242, 2002-2004 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - 820250, 1991-1994 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - 820251, 2003-2006 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    County of Burlington
  - 820319, 2000-2003 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    The City of Chicago
  - 820311, 2001-2006 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    County of San Diego
  - 820318, 2001-2004 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    County of Cook
  - 820319, 1996-1999 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - 820312, 1978-1988 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    County of Allegheny
  - 820256, 2001-2003 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    County of Kent
  - 820257, 2004-2005 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    Department of Correction State of Washington
  - 820265, 2002-2005 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    Westmoreland County
  - 820266, 2003-2006 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    Leon Educational Support Association
  - 820272, 2002-2005 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    Miami Dade County Florida
  - 820287, 2001-2004 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    Metropolitan Government Nashville and Davidson County
  - 820292, 2004-2006 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    Board of Commissioner Montg. Co. Ohio
  - 820297, 2000-2003 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - 820320, 1999-2002 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    NJ Transit Bus Operations Inc.
  - 820321, 2000-2003 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    State of Rhode Island
  - 820322, 2001-2004 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Folder List Index Box # 42 (Box 42, Folder 28)
- Public agreements: Code nos.820795-820854 (Box 43)
  - 820795, 2002-2006 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    County of Sacramento
  - 820797, 1998-1999 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    County of Hennepin
  - 820798, 2001-2006 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - 820803, 2001-2004 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    School Board of Escambia County
  - 820805, 2003-2006 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - 820806, 2002-2005 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    Miami-Dade County/Water and Sewer Department
  - 820813, 2003-2005 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - 820817, 2003-2006 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    County of Clark
  - 820818, 1984-1987 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    County of Cook/Sheriff of Cook County
  - 820820, 2003-2006 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    University Medical Center
  - 820821, 1996-2005 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    County of Oneida
  - 820822, 2001-2004 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - 820855, 1997-2005 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    District School Board of Pasco County
  - 820826, 2003-2006 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - 820828, 1991-1998 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    Commonwealth of Pennsylvania
  - 820830, 2002-2005 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    School Board of Okaloosa County
  - 820831, 2002-2004 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    Lincoln Public Schools
  - 820832, 2002-2004 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    Northshore School District #417
  - 820834, 2001-2005 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    Santa Clara Valley Transit Authority
  - 820835, 2003-2005 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    Eugene School District #4J
  - 820833, 2002-2003 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    Tulsa Public Schools
  - 820836, 2002-2005 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    Sweetwater Union High School District
  - 820838, 2001 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    County of Essex
  - 820839, 2001-2003 (Box 43, Folder 24)
    Metropolitan Nashville Board of Public Education
  - 820840, 2003-2006 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - 820841, 2003-2004 (Box 43, Folder 26)
    City of Tulsa
  - 820843, 2005-2006 (Box 43, Folder 27)
    School Board of Brevard County
  - 820844, 2004-2005 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - 820845, 1991-1994 (Box 43, Folder 29)
    Metropolitan Public Health Trust
  - 820846, 2004-2006 (Box 43, Folder 30)
    Multnomah County
  - 820847, 1999-2003 (Box 43, Folder 31)
    Superintendent of Schools
  - 820848, 2003-2006 (Box 43, Folder 32)
    Board of Education Los Angeles
  - 820851, 2002-2005 (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - 820852, 2002-2005 (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - 820857, 1998-2001 (Box 43, Folder 35)
    Knox County Board of Education
  - 820860, 2003-2005 (Box 43, Folder 36)
    Board of Education Washington County
  - 820861, 2005-2006 (Box 43, Folder 37)
    Davis Board of Education
  - 820863, 2003-2005 (Box 43, Folder 38)
  - 820864, 2005-2006 (Box 43, Folder 39)
  - 820865, 2005-2006 (Box 43, Folder 40)
  - 820866, 2004-2005 (Box 43, Folder 41)
  - 820867, 1994-1997 (Box 43, Folder 42)
    Poway Unified School District
  - 820868, 2001-2004 (Box 43, Folder 43)
  - 820869, 2003-2005 (Box 43, Folder 44)
  - 820870, 2003-2006 (Box 43, Folder 45)
  - 820018, 2003-2004 (Box 43, Folder 46)
    Board of Education USD 259
  - 830038, 2003-2005 (Box 43, Folder 47)
    Unknown
  - 820849, 2002-2005 (Box 43, Folder 48)
  - 820850, 1983-2005 (Box 43, Folder 49)
  - 820854, 1991-1994 (Box 43, Folder 50)
  - Folder List Index Box # 43 (Box 43, Folder 51)
- Public agreements: Code nos.800122-800218 (Box 44)
  - 800122, 2000-2003 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    July 1 2000 - June 30 2003
  - 800136, 2001-2004 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    July 1 2001 - June 30 2004
  - 800137, 2001-2004 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - 800138, 1999-2003 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    4/1/1999 - 3/31/2003
  - 800139, 1999-2003 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - 800141, 2002-2003 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - 800142, 2004-2006 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    7/1/2004 - 6/30/2006
  - 800143, 2003-2006 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    7/1/2003 - 6/30/2006
  - 800144, 2000-2003 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    January 1 2000 - December 31 2003
  - 800148, 2003-2006 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - 800153, 1979-1981 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    March 1 1979 - June 30 1981
  - 800154, 2002-2003 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    August 5 2002 - June 30 2003
  - 800155, 1999-2003 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    July 1 1999 - June 30 2003
  - 800163, 2003-2005 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    July 1 2003 - June 30 2005
  - 800164, 2001-2004 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    December 1 2001 - November 30 2004
  - 800165, 2003-2006 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    July 1 2003 - June 30 2006
  - 800167, 1999-2003 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - 800172, 1999-2003 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - 800175, 2002-2005 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    July 2002 - June 2005
  - 800176, 1997-2000 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    July 1 1997 - June 30 2000
  - 800183, 2005 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    June 30 2005
  - 800192, 2003-2006 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - 800199, 2003-2006 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    3/1/2003 - 2/28/2006
  - 800200, 2002-2005 (Box 44, Folder 24)
    July1 2002 - June 30 2005
  - 800205, 2000-2003 (Box 44, Folder 25)
    11/13/2000 - 9/30/2003
  - 800206, 2003-2006 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - 800208, 2002-2005 (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - 800209, 2003-2006 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - 800218, 2000-2003 (Box 44, Folder 29)
- Private agreements: Code nos.1231-1627 (Box 45)
  - 1231, 1986-1996 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    Thilmany Pulp and Paper
  - 1246, 1989-1998 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    S.D. Warren Company
  - 1261, 1971-1997 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    Kimberly Clark
  - 1297, 1985-2001 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    P.H. Glatfelter Co.
  - 1300, 1986-1998 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    Champion International
  - 1301, 1987-1995 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    Weyerhaeuser Company
  - 1303, 1983-1987 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    S.D. Warren Co. Scott Paper
  - 1438, 1971-2001 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    Time One
  - 1451, 1976-2001 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    Washington Post
  - 1619, 1993-2001 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - 1626, 1971-1994 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    North America Rayon Corporation
  - 1627, 1973-2004 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    Celanese
  - Folder List Index Box # 46 (Box 45, Folder 13)
- Public agreements: Code nos.800219-800287 (Box 46)
  - 800219, 1995-1999 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    July 1 1995 - June 30 1999
  - 800220, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    6/2005
  - 800221, 2003-2006 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    10/1/2003 - 9/30/2006
  - 800228, 2004-2006 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    July 1 2004 - December 31 2006
  - 800234, 2003-2005 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    7/1/2003 - 6/30/2005
  - 800240, 2001-2004 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - 800241, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    6/30/2005
  - 800242, 2003-2005 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - 800243, 2003-2005 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - 800244, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    6/6/2002
  - 800245, 2005-2007 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    7/1/2005 - 6/30/2007
  - 800246, 2003-2005 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - 800248, 2003-2005 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - 800249, 1999-2003 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - 800250, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - 800255, 2002-2005 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    November 1 2002 - October 31 2005
  - 800260, 2000-2003 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    September 1 2000 - August 31 2003
  - 800262, 2004-2006 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    July 1 2004 - June 30 2006
  - 800264, 2003-2005 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - 800265, 2003-2004 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    July 30 2003 - September 30 2004
  - 800266, 2003-2006 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - 800267, 2001-2003 (Box 46, Folder 22)
    7/1/2001 - 6/30/2003
  - 800270, 2002-2003 (Box 46, Folder 23)
    2/1/2002 - 6/30/2003
  - 800271, 2001-2004 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - 800272, 2000-2004 (Box 46, Folder 25)
    7/1/2000 - 6/30/2004
  - 800275, 2002-2006 (Box 46, Folder 26)
    7/1/2002 - 6/30/2006
  - 800279, 2001-2004 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - 800281, 1999-2002 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - 800282, 2005-2006 (Box 46, Folder 29)
    January 1 2005 - December 31 2006
  - 800283, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - 800284, 2001-2003 (Box 46, Folder 31)
    7/23/2001 - 6/30/2003
  - 800285, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 32)
    1/27/1989
  - 800286, 2002-2005 (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - 800287, 2003-2005 (Box 46, Folder 34)
    July 2003 - June 2005
  - Folder List Index Box # 46 (Box 46, Folder 35)
- Private agreements: Code nos.K3-K1459 (Box 47)
  - 3, 1995-2002 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Weyerhaeuser Paper Co.
  - 3, 1995-2002 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - 4, 2002-2005 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Honeywell Fed Manufacturing
  - 4, 2002-2005 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Honeywell Fed. Manufacturing
  - 8, 2003-2006 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Raytheon Missile Systems
  - 8, 2003-2006 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - 9, 2002-2005 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    Lockheed Martin Space Systems
  - 9, 2002-2005 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    Lockheed Martin Space System
  - 12, 2000-2005 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    Pathmark Stores
  - 14, 2001-2005 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    Midwest Generation
  - 18, 2000-2005 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    Olin Corp.
  - 22, 2000-2004 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    Vought Aircraft
  - 23, 2002-2006 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    NYC Heavy Construction
  - 202, 2003-2006 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    Chicago Midwest Meat
  - 206, 2002-2006 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    Keebler
  - 210, 2002-2006 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    Kraft Foods
  - 253, 2003-2006 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    California Processors
  - 254, 2003-2006 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    Campbell Soup
  - 286, 1999-2003 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    Grain Millers Union
  - 293, 1990-2004 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    Amalgamated Sugar
  - 298, 2002-2005 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    Michigan Sugar
  - 369, 2001-2005 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - 385, 1998-2003 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    Brach and Brock Confections
  - 402, 2001-2006 (Box 47, Folder 20)
    Tropicana
  - 422, 2003-2006 (Box 47, Folder 21)
    Super Foods
  - 423, 2002-2006 (Box 47, Folder 22)
    Swift and Company
  - 444, 2003-2006 (Box 47, Folder 23)
    Tysons Foods
  - 445, 2002-2006 (Box 47, Folder 24)
    Swift
  - 480, 2003-2006 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - 506, 2003-2006 (Box 47, Folder 26)
    Loullard Tobacco
  - 513, 2000-2003 (Box 47, Folder 27)
    Brown and Williamson
  - 515, 1997-2003 (Box 47, Folder 28)
    Phillip Morris
  - 602, 1997-2002 (Box 47, Folder 29)
    Dan River
  - 612, 2001-2006 (Box 47, Folder 30)
    Fieldcrest Cannon
  - 824, 1994-1997 (Box 47, Folder 31)
    New York Coat and Suit
  - 828, 2001-2004 (Box 47, Folder 32)
    New York Skirt and Sportswear
  - 857, 2001-2004 (Box 47, Folder 33)
    Plastic Soft Materials Manufacturers Association
  - 858, 2001-2004 (Box 47, Folder 34)
    Atlantic Apparel
  - 860, 2003-2006 (Box 47, Folder 35)
    Pleaters, Stitchers and Embroiderers
  - 867, 2004-2006 (Box 47, Folder 36)
    Levi Strauss
  - 876, 2001-2004 (Box 47, Folder 37)
    Greater Blouse Skirt
  - 1033, 1998-2004 (Box 47, Folder 38)
    International Paper
  - 1131, 1997-2002 (Box 47, Folder 39)
    District Council of NYC
  - 1200, 1999-2005 (Box 47, Folder 40)
    Consolidated Papers
  - 1217, 2000-2005 (Box 47, Folder 41)
  - 1221, 2000-2005 (Box 47, Folder 42)
    Mead
  - 1226, 2000-2006 (Box 47, Folder 43)
    Longview Fibre Co.
  - 1266, 2000-2006 (Box 47, Folder 44)
    Georgia Pacific
  - 1281, 1991-2006 (Box 47, Folder 45)
    Union Camp Corporation Fine Paper Division
  - 1282, 1999-2005 (Box 47, Folder 46)
    Fort James Corp/Georgia Pacific
  - 1293, 2000-2006 (Box 47, Folder 47)
  - 1309, 1995-2002 (Box 47, Folder 48)
  - 1417, 2003-2006 (Box 47, Folder 49)
    Dex Media
  - 1419, 2001-2005 (Box 47, Folder 50)
    Metropolitan Lithographics
  - 1451, 2002-2005 (Box 47, Folder 51)
  - 1457, 1998-2005 (Box 47, Folder 52)
    No California Newspaper Guild
  - 1458, 2001-2006 (Box 47, Folder 53)
    Quebecor World Kingsport
  - 1459, 2001-2006 (Box 47, Folder 54)
    National Sample Card Manufacturing
  - Folder List Index Box # 47 (Box 47, Folder 55)
- Private agreements: Code nos.7712-8139 (Box 48)
  - 7712, 2001-2006 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    1/1/2001 - 6/1/2006
  - 7906, 2003-2006 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    February 1 2003 - December 31 2006
  - 7915, 2003-2006 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - 7929, 2000 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    October 1 2000
  - 7946, 2002-2006 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    June 1 2002 - September 30 2006
  - 7958, 2003-2006 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    10/30/2003 - 10/29/2006
  - 7962, 2002-2006 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    September 1 2002 - August 31 2006
  - 7964, 2003-2006 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    October 14 2003 - October 13 2006
  - 7967, 2002-2006 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    May 1 2002 - April 30 2006
  - 7981, 2003-2006 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    March 1 2003 - February 28 2006
  - 7984, 2002-2006 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    October 1 2002 - December 31 2006
  - 7993, 2002-2006 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    March 16 2002 - March 15 2006
  - 7994, 2003-2006 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    February 24 2003 - February 26 2006
  - 8003, 2001-2006 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    July 1 2001 - June 30 2006
  - 8011, 2001-2006 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - 8015, 2004-2006 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    June 9 2004 - December 1 2006
  - 8019, 2004-2006 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    October 1 2004 - September 30 2006
  - 8022, 2002-2006 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    9/30/2002 - 12/19/2006
  - 8026, 2004-2006 (Box 48, Folder 19)
    May 4 2004 - December 31 2006
  - 8027, 2000-2006 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - 8033, 2003-2006 (Box 48, Folder 21)
    September 1 2003 - August 31 2006
  - 8035, 2001-2006 (Box 48, Folder 22)
    June1 2001 - May 31 2006
  - 8044, 2000-2006 (Box 48, Folder 23)
    October 1 2000 - September 30 2006
  - 8092, 2002-2006 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - 8071, 2003-2006 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - 8073, 2001-2006 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - 8075, 2003-2006 (Box 48, Folder 27)
    April 1 2003 - March 31 2006
  - 8076, 2001-2006 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - 8091, 2001-2006 (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - 8095, 2003-2006 (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - 8100, 2004-2006 (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - 8106, 2003-2006 (Box 48, Folder 32)
    June 1 2003 - May 27 2006
  - 8107, 2003-2006 (Box 48, Folder 33)
    June1 2003 - May 27 2006
  - 8108, 2001-2006 (Box 48, Folder 34)
  - 8110, 2003-2006 (Box 48, Folder 35)
    December 1 2003 - November 30 2006
  - 8113, 2003-2006 (Box 48, Folder 36)
  - 8116, 2003-2006 (Box 48, Folder 37)
    August 6 2003 - June 30 2006
  - 8117, 2001-2006 (Box 48, Folder 38)
    June 3 2001 - June 3 2006
  - 8133, 2003-2006 (Box 48, Folder 39)
  - 8136, 2000-2006 (Box 48, Folder 40)
    October 2 2000 - July 1 2006
  - 8139, 2002-2006 (Box 48, Folder 41)
  - Folder List Index Box # 48 (Box 48, Folder 42)
- Private agreements: Code nos.6873-7416 (Box 49)
  - 6873, 1998 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    6/1998
  - 6874, 1994-1997 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    5/29/1994 - 11/4/1997
  - 6877, 1990-2000 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    2/1990 - 2/2000
  - 6880, 1993-2003 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    11/19/1993 - 8/1/2003
  - 6885, 1987-1989 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    5/1987 - 5/6/1989
  - 6887, 1989-1992 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    3/1989 - 2/1992
  - 6890, 1993-1996 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    9/1993 - 9/1996
  - 6916, 1972-1990 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    7/1972 - 6/1990
  - 6935, 1991-2000 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    7/1991 - 9/2000
  - 8, 1990-1999 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    10/23/1990 - 10/25/1999
  - 7094, 1995-1996 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    1/1995 - 11/1996
  - 7117, 1966-1986 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    3/1966 - 3/1986
  - 7142, 1994-2002 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    9/1994 - 8/2002
  - 7300, 1999-2002 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    7/1999 - 7/2002
  - 7307, 1999-2002 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - 7350, 1995-2001 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    10/1995 - 12/2001
  - 7402, 1993-1996 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    3/1993 - 3/1996
  - 7404, 1995-2001 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    9/1995 - 9/2001
  - 7504, 1973-1988 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    11/1973 - 11/1988
  - 7504, 1991-2001 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    8/1991 - 11/2001
  - 7414, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 21)
    10/17/2001; 86 pages
  - 7415, 1970-1994 (Box 49, Folder 22)
    1/1970 - 1/1994
  - 7416, 1987-1999 (Box 49, Folder 23)
    10/1987 - 10/1999
  - Folder List Index Box # 49 (Box 49, Folder 24)
- Private agreements: Code nos.7914-7958 (Box 50)
  - 7914, 1993-2002 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    6/1993 - 6/2002
  - 7915, 1982-2000 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    7/1982 - 7/2000
  - 7926, 1969-1991 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    1/1969 - 7/1/1991
  - 7930, 1974-1998 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    7/1974 - 6/1998
  - 7939, 1984-1997 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    4/1984 - 9/1997
  - 7941, 1975-1996 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    11/1975 - 12/1996
  - 7948, 1974-1992 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    7/1974 - 7/1992
  - 7953, 1976-1990 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    1/1967 - 6/1990
  - 7958, 1982-1997 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    2/1982 - 3/1997
  - Folder List Index Box # 50 (Box 50, Folder 10)
- Private agreements: Code nos.K6056-K6713 (Box 51)
  - 6056, 2002-2005 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    Cincinnati Gas and Electric
  - 6058, 2000-2004 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    Consolidated Edison
  - 6059, 2000-2005 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    Consumers Energy
  - 6060, 2000-2005 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    Dayton Power and Light
  - 6061, 1999-2004 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    Detroit Edison
  - 6063, 2003-2006 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    Illinois Power
  - 6064, 2002-2004 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    Jersey's Central Power
  - 6065, 2001-2004 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    Keyspan
  - 6066, 2001-2004 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - 6068, 2001-2004 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    Niagara Mohawk Power
  - 6070, 2000-2005 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    NY State Electric and Gas
  - 6074, 2001-2005 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    Peoples Energy
  - 6075, 2003-2006 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    Public Service Company on Colorado
  - 6076, 2002-2005 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    Public Service Company of Colorado
  - 6077, 2001-2004 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    San Diego Gas and Electric
  - 6081, 2003-2006 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    Wisconsin Public Service
  - 6096, 2003-2004 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    Duke Power
  - 6106, 2001-2004 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    Alabama Power
  - 6301, 2003-2006 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    Bon Macy's
  - 6317, 1999-2002 (Box 51, Folder 20)
    Lumber Industry
  - 6325, 2000-2005 (Box 51, Folder 21)
    Ready Mix
  - 6336, 2003-2004 (Box 51, Folder 22)
    Kroger
  - 6344, 1995-2004 (Box 51, Folder 23)
    Giant Eagle Markets
  - 6345, 1995-2003 (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - 6354, 1997-2003 (Box 51, Folder 25)
    Dominick's
  - 6359, 2002-2006 (Box 51, Folder 26)
    Safeway
  - 6360, 1997-2002 (Box 51, Folder 27)
    Metro/Basics/Food-A-Rama
  - 6365, 2001-2005 (Box 51, Folder 28)
    Zallie Supermarkets
  - 6372, 2002-2005 (Box 51, Folder 29)
  - 6376, 1998-2002 (Box 51, Folder 30)
    King Kullen Food
  - 6377, 2002-2006 (Box 51, Folder 31)
    The Stop-N-Shop Foods
  - 6378, 2005-2006 (Box 51, Folder 32)
    D'Agostino
  - 6541, 2001-2006 (Box 51, Folder 33)
    May Codba Filene's
  - 6580, 1999-2006 (Box 51, Folder 34)
    Macy's Northeast
  - 6590, 2002-2005 (Box 51, Folder 35)
    NBC Merchants
  - 6592, 2002-2006 (Box 51, Folder 36)
    Allied Employer
  - 6701, 2001-2005 (Box 51, Folder 37)
    ACME
  - 6703, 2002-2005 (Box 51, Folder 38)
    Cleveland Food
  - 6704, 2002-2005 (Box 51, Folder 39)
  - 6707, 1999-2003 (Box 51, Folder 40)
    Albertson's
  - 6709, 2001-2005 (Box 51, Folder 41)
    Kines Supermarkets
  - 6711, 2001-2005 (Box 51, Folder 42)
    Tops Markets Midstate Division
  - 6712, 2001-2005 (Box 51, Folder 43)
    Tops Markets Buffalo Division
  - 6713, 1996-2001 (Box 51, Folder 44)
    Tops Markets Rochester Division
  - Folder List Index Box # 51 (Box 51, Folder 45)
- Private agreements: Code nos.K7417-K7532 (Box 52)
  - 7417, 2001-2005 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    November 3 2001 - November 5 2005
  - 7419, 2000 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    9/13/2000
  - 7421, 2004-2006 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    January 1 2004 - December 31 2006
  - 7423, 2002-2005 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    October 27 2002 - October 22 2005
  - 7424, 2001-2004 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    June 1 2001 - May 31 2004
  - 7425, 2002-2005 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    September 1 2002 - August 31 2005
  - 7426, 1999-2003 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    8/1/1999 - 7/31/2003
  - 7429, 2002-2005 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    May 1 2002 - April 30 2005
  - 7511, 1999-2004 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    8/14/1999 - 8/14/2004